noteburner.com 2012-11-23

# Noteburner provides the best DRM removal software, convert m4p to mp3, m4v to mp4, m4a to mp3, m4b to mp3, wma to mp3 etc.

### Privacy of NoteBurner - We value you as a customer and value your privacy

Our goal in handling information provided to us in connection with the processing of transactions on our Website is to comply with applicable data privacy laws and to offer users of our Website notice, choice, consent, security, data integrity, access and enforcement with regard to personal information provided to us by individuals in conjunction with those transactions.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.

We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to our commitment to protecting your privacy. We will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever.

To remove DRM protection of iTunes audio book on Mac, NoteBurner Audiobook converter will be your best choice. The audiobook converter can convert your audio books to unprotected MP3 and AAC format. For AAC output, you can even keep the chapters information which allows you to choose favorite chapter to listen on any AAC playable media players and mobile phones.

#### What information do we collect? What do we use it for?

We partner with PayPal, RegNow and SWREG to provide you safe and fast e-commerce services. When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you.

Actually, We dose not deal with the transaction and will not get your credit card information. We only keep your user name, email address and the info of the product you purchase. This information is kept for customer services purpose only.

#### How do 3rd party credit card processors protect your information?

**Paypal**

PayPal is the safer, easier way to pay and get paid online that has been in operation since 1998. It has become a global leader in online payment solutions with more than 164 million accounts worldwide. We uses Pal pay to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase. Read the [Privacy Policy of PayPal](https://www.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside)

**RegNow**

RegNow is an industry leader in providing e-commerce processing services and online credit card processing for vendors and authors of PC and Macintosh software, freeware, shareware, electronic art, shopping cart, ecommerce provider and other data. We used RegNow to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase. Read the [Privacy Policy of RegNow](http://www.regnow.com/privacy.html)

**SWREG**

SWREG offers merchant accounts, a paypal alternative, affordable ecommerce, payment processing, ecommerce solution, and an online software store with the ability to sell shareware. SWREG offers numerous customer payment options including: Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Discover, JCB, Switch, Solo, Paypal, US Check, UK Cheque, International Money Order, EFT, ACH, BACS, Wire Transfer, Credit Card by Phone or Fax with 16 toll-free international numbers. Read the [Privacy Policy of SWREG](http://www.swreg.org/privacy.htm)

#### About cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, "cookies" will be used. A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our web site and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.
